<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bạch Triết - a awesome chief</title>
    <description>This is a personal blog jutsu write for Bạch Triết, just a testing version !!
</description>
    <link>https://bachtrietchief.github.iohttp://bachtriet.github.io</link>
    <atom:link href="http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:38:49 +0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:38:49 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.7</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>hellosdfsdf</title>
        <description> 
 </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-4/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-4/</guid>
        
        <category>sexy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>deep </title>
        <description> &lt;p&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has made a mess of the present and clouded any visions of the future, but at least—as artworks of our era keep insisting—the past is there to guide us. Taylor Swift, for example, has been thinking about her grandfather fighting in World War II. On “Epiphany,” from the superstar’s surprise-release album, Folklore, Swift sings of him on a 1942 battlefield, attending to a comrade bleeding out. Her voice is a translucent beam; her syllables fall slowly like ash. But by verse two, she’s singing from somewhere else: a 2020 medical ward of plastic sheaths and labored breathing. Swift’s singing as someone else, too—a nurse attending to a faltering patient. “Doc,” she says, “I think she’s crashing out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**A song like this doesn’t seem like it should work**. Here’s a woman of great privilege equating two traumas that aren’t her own while using the ever-dicey metaphor of war to describe a viral pandemic. But Swift writes with a care and empathy that feel almost priestly. The soldier and the medical worker, overburdened by horror, both get “only 20 minutes to sleep” and yet dream “of some epiphany—just one single glimpse of relief.” __Swift__ doesn’t describe the epiphany. We have to dream it for ourselves.
  More Stories&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Song of the Summer Is in Chaos
  Spencer Kornhaber
  Hip-Hop Won’t Stop Protecting Alleged Abusers
  Hannah Giorgis
  Revelers at the 2018 Coachella music festival
  Pop Music’s Version of Life Doesn’t Exist Anymore
  Spencer Kornhaber&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asking others to do the dreaming is new for the 30-year-old Swift, one of the 21st century’s canniest exhibitionists. By unpacking her teenage diary with a country twang and then litigating celebrity romances over synth-pop, her first seven albums fed a public hungry for stars to let the world into their living room. But one of the delights of Folklore, an audacious and almost-too-rich feast of an album, is that Swift moves away from a solid sense of the first person. There are fictional stories, there are historical stories, there are personal stories—and there are all three in the space of single songs. “In isolation,” she explained on Instagram, “my imagination has run wild.” The outward-looking approach has made her a better writer, and it might just create better listeners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With its woodsy black-and-white art, not to mention its title, Folklore advertises itself as an expected pop-star maneuver: the “back to basics” or “stripped down” revelation. But the album’s more complex than that, and does not conjure the image of Swift slumped over a guitar for an acoustic set. With the producers Aaron Dessner (of the indie band The National) and Jack Antonoff (the rock singer turned pop-star whisperer), she swims through intricate classical and folk instrumentation largely organized by the gridded logic of electronic music. Melancholy singers of ’90s rock radio such as Natalie Merchant and Sarah McLachlan seem to guide Swift’s choices, as do contemporaries such as Lana Del Rey and Lorde. The overall effect is eerie, gutting, and nostalgic. If Folklore is not apt for summer fun, it is apt for a year in which rambunctious cheer and mass sing-alongs have few venues in which to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The transition from last year’s ultra-fluorescent Lover takes some getting used to, though. Dessner’s ominous chords, delicate rhythms, and smudgy instrumental loops have in the past complemented singers such as The National’s Matt Berninger, whose surreal poetry documents inarticulable feelings. But Swift is an artist defined by clarity; when she attempts ambiguity, it’s by planting solvable riddles. Even so, Dessner’s sound often suits her like a finely knitted cape, as with the grooving plucked strings of “Invisible String.” But sometimes the songs’ solemnity seems forced, especially during the shaky first third of the album. The conversational opener, “The 1,” has a suspicious whiff of Ed Sheeran. The lead single, “Cardigan,” is swamped by sepia. The Bon Iver duet, “Exile,” plods in the manner of bad musical theater.&lt;/p&gt;
 </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-3/</guid>
        
        <category>pciture</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>sexy picture</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-2/</guid>
        
        <category>sexy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>cook is art</title>
        <description> &lt;h1&gt;Hello&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;World&lt;/p&gt;
 </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://bachtriet.github.iohttps://bachtrietchief.github.io/2020/10/22/jekyll-1/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
